- question: "What are the two basic sections of an Ansible playbook?"
  options:
    - "play and tasks"
    - "play and roles"
    - "roles and collections"
    - "tasks and collections"
  correct: "play and tasks"
  day: 2

- question: "What do you find to the left of a colon in YAML?"
  options:
    - "Key"
    - "Value"
    - "Array"
    - "Dictionary"
  correct: "Key"
  day: 2

- question: "What Ansible module would you use to check the value of a variable?"
  options:
    - "var"
    - "loop"
    - "debug"
    - "copy"
  correct: "debug"
  day: 2

- question: "What data serialization technique is a subset of YAML?"
  options:
    - "Toml"
    - "JSON"
    - "Lists"
    - "Python"
  correct: "JSON"
  day: 2

- question: "What Ansible playbook section actually does the work?"
  options:
    - "name"
    - "tasks"
    - "vars"
    - "handlers"
  correct: "tasks"
  day: 2

- question: "What is the variable used to make a loop in Ansible?"
  options:
    - "vars"
    - "gather_facts"
    - "item"
    - "debug"
  correct: "item"
  day: 3

- question: "What characters are used to represent a Python list?"
  options:
    - "{}"
    - "()"
    - "[]"
    - "\"\""
  correct: "[]"
  day: 3

- question: "What characters are used to represent a Python dictionary?"
  options:
    - "[]"
    - "\"\""
    - "()"
    - "{}"
  correct: "{}"
  day: 3

- question: "What is the first thing you should do when attempting to access an API?"
  options:
    - "Read the API documentation."
    - "Read the docs about the API."
    - "Search for documentation about the API."
    - "Read the docs read the docs read the docs."
  correct: "Read the API documentation."
  day: 3

- question: "What does the Assert module help create in a playbook?"
  options:
    - "tasks"
    - "prechecks"
    - "play"
    - "handlers"
  correct: "prechecks"
  day: 3

- question: "What can installing an Ansible collection give you?"
  options:
    - "A series of roles and tasks."
    - "A group of playbooks."
    - "Access to multiple customized modules."
    - "All of the above."
  correct: "All of the above."
  day: 4

- question: "What does the redfish_info module do?"
  options:
    - "Allow you to make changes to the config file."
    - "Gather facts about redfish hosts."
    - "Issue commands to remote hosts."
    - "Trick question. It doesn't exist."
  correct: "Gather facts about redfish hosts."
  day: 4

- question: "If you wanted to create a new group of hosts what file would you configure?"
  options:
    - "Ansible config file."
    - "Python config file."
    - "Inventory file."
    - "A text file."
  correct: "Inventory file."
  day: 4

- question: "Is it possible to have more than one inventory file?"
  options:
    - "Yes"
    - "No"
  correct: "Yes"
  day: 4

- question: "There will always be a module that allows Ansible to gather facts about a remote target."
  options:
    - "True"
    - "False"
  correct: "True"
  day: 5

- question: "Writing Pre-Checks are part of following best practices."
  options:
    - "True"
    - "False"
    - "Maybe?"
    - "I don't follow best practices."
  correct: "True"
  day: 5

- question: "What Ansible command is used to create a Role?"
  options:
    - "ansible-playbook"
    - "ansible-galaxy role install"
    - "ansible-galaxy role init"
    - "ansible-doc role init"
  correct: "ansible-galaxy role init"
  day: 5

- question: "What do the Block and Rescue keywords provide?"
  options:
    - "A way to group tasks together."
    - "Allows for a method to import tasks from a different file."
    - "Allows you to copy roles from other files."
    - "Provides a safety net in case of task failure."
  correct: "Provides a safety net in case of task failure."
  day: 5
